>> Jem Young: 什么是防火墙?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: What is a firewall?
别再看这个定义了
Don't look at the definition yet.
防火墙是什么 ?
What is a firewall?
你以前可能听过这个词
You've probably heard the term before.
嗯。
Yeah.
>> 扬声器 2: 它是网络安全性基础结构，允许或
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's network security
infrastructure that either allows or
阻止请求。
blocks requests.
>> Jem Young: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah.
你说的萨姆
Sam that you say?
> > Sam: 不，这是外围安全技术，所以
&gt;&gt; Sam: No,
it's a perimeter security technique, so
您可以根据请求的来源和来源
you either allow requests in or out
depending on how they're originating and
他们是什么港口协议是什么
what port they're on and
what the protocol is.
>> Jem Young: 对，她说的更详细。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah,
what she said, more verbose.
我喜欢你在定义事物时，永远不会太详细。
I like it, you can never be too
verbose when you're defining things.
防火墙，短语来自称为防火墙的实际物理设备，
A firewall, the phrase comes from the
actual physical device called a firewall,
你的车有防火墙
your car has a firewall.
所以在引擎和你坐在你车里的地方
So between the engine and
where you sit in your car,
这就是所谓的防火墙
that's what's known as a firewall.
所以如果引擎着火了，火就不会蔓延到发动机。
So if the engine gets on fire,
the fire won't spread into the engine.
或者它会减速足够的建筑有防火墙所以如果有防火墙的话
Or it will slow down enough building have
firewalls so that if there is a fire it
它不会完全阻止事情的发生只会让它变慢你就能解决它
doesn't prevent things completely, it just
slows it down enough so you can fix it.
这就是防火墙的功能。
And that's what a firewall does.
他们不是无敌的
They are not invulnerable,
总有办法让所有人都在防火墙上运行
there's always ways around them cuz
everybody's running a firewall now.
但人们还是被黑了
But people still get hacked.
但足够让人慢下来，震慑民众。
But it's enough to slow people down and
deter people.
我要用思科的定义了大家都这么说
I'll use the Cisco definition, and
it's pretty much what everybody said.
它是一个网络安全设备，监控进出的网络流量，
It's a network secure device that monitors
incoming and outgoing network traffic and
根据特定频率决定是否阻塞该流量，
it decides whether or not to block that
traffic based on certain frequencies,
有一套标准的
there's a certain set of standards.
有软件防火墙和硬件防火墙。
There is software firewalls and
there's hardware firewalls.
通常大多数人都在运行我们的消费等级。
Generally most people
are running our consumer grade.
我们都是软件防火墙
We're all running software firewalls.
我们的 Mac OS X 在 Windows 中建立了防火墙，防火墙内置了防火墙。
Our Mac OS X has a firewall built
in Windows has firewall built in.
因为我们不想把所有港口都开放给每个人
It's because we don't wanna open
all of our ports to everybody.
因为如果你这样做，不管你喜欢，我在使用 SSH
Because if you do that, it doesn't
matter if your like, I'm using SSH and
我的系统也没什么值钱的东西
there's nothing else my
system worth stealing.
在那里可能有个漏洞
There could be
a vulnerability in there and
它只是在缩小它的攻击表面
it's just narrowing that attack surface.
以及防火墙的映像。
And an image of a firewall.
我喜欢
I like that.
>> Jem Young: 因此，让我们运行 nmap ，因为我之前谈到过端口。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So let's run nmap
because I talked about ports earlier.
nmap 是端口扫描程序，它可以运行整个
An nmap is a port scanner and
what it does is it can run over an entire
IP 地址的范围，它仅检查打开的端口。
range of IP addresses and
it just checks for open ports.
首先我们要做的就是安装 nmap。
So first thing we're gonna do
is we're gonna install nmap.
>> Jem Young: Sudo apt 安装 nmap ( 如果尚未安装) 。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Sudo apt install nmap
if it's not already installed.
>> Jem Young: So sudo apt install
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So sudo apt install
>> Jem Young: 我将抓取服务器的 IP 地址。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And I'm gonna grab
the IP address of my server.
所以就在这儿
So, it's here.
收到。
Copy that.
>> Sam: 您打算以远程方式在本地对服务器运行此操作，或者
&gt;&gt; Sam: You intending that we run this
locally against our server remotely or
在服务器上。
from the server.
>> Jem Young: 您可以在服务器上运行，可以从服务器运行。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: You could run on the server,
you can run it from not your server.
其实这件事不重要
It actually doesn't matter in this case.
但是运行它，在本地运行，您应该知道端口在哪里。
But running it yeah, running it locally
you should know where your ports are.
但这只是一个很好的视觉化。
But it's just a good visualization.
>> Jem Young: 是的， Sam 是正确的，我们的服务器正在与我们的服务器
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes and Sam is right where
we're on our server running against our
自己的服务器。
own server.
您可以从服务器注销并针对您的服务器运行
You can log out of your server and
run against your server and
结果就一样了
the results will be the same.
>> Jem Young: 现在你可能看到了
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And right now you're
probably seeing something along that
你应该看看这个
you should see actually exactly this.
您已打开端口 22 ，即 SSH。
You have port 22 open, that's SSH.
因此，这允许我们登录和注销我们的服务器。
So, that's allows us to log in and
out our server.
我们端口 80 是我们的 http 服务器。
We port 80 which is our http server.
然后我们就有 3000 口因为它是在我们的默认情况下开放的
And then we have port 3000 because
it's open by default when we
启动了我们的快速服务器。
started our express server.
现在，让我们与 sV 一起运行 nmap ，以获取更多详细信息。
Now let's run nmap with sV to
get a little bit more detail.
所以 nmap >> Jem Young: And
So nmap
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And
这得花点时间
this is gonna take a little bit more time.
sV 命令会让我们更详细地了解
The sV command is gonna give us more
detail about what exact processes
正在这些端口上运行这些端口和服务。
are running on those and
services are running on those ports.
也许会有
And it might take
就在第二天
a second ago.
所以， 22 号端口几乎都是 SSH的。
So, port 22 is pretty
pretty much always SSH.
这是缺省的 48 个 Windows HTTP。
It's the default 48 windows HTTP.
3000 是一个随机的港口，我们只为我们的中间产品选择了一个。
For 3000 was a random port we chose
just for our express middle ware.
但是，运行此开放式源代码命令允许我端口扫描 IP 地址。
But running this open source command
allows me to port scan an IP address.
但不仅仅是这样，它还告诉我他们正在运行的软件和版本。
But not only that, it tells me the exact
software and version that they're running.
那么为什么有用呢 ?
So why is that useful?
或者为什么这么危险
Or why that dangerous?
嗯。
Yes.
>> 扬声器 2: 非常容易查找已知漏洞和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: it's very easy to
look up known vulnerabilities and
开始尝试过
start trying to get through.
>> Jem Young: 如果有已知的利用 NGINX 1.14的话。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Precisely, if there
was a known exploit for NGINX 1.14.
我可以很容易地发现这一点
I can find that out really, really easily.
然后你说没人会知道我是否没有拍我的 NGINX 版本
And then you say like, no one will know
if I haven't patched my NGINX version.
都是，人都在港口跑。
They do,
people are running at port all the time.
现在， CPU 资源非常少，无法在整个因特网上运行端口扫描，
It takes very little CPU resources now to
run a port scan over the entire Internet,
人们不断地这样做。
and people are doing this constantly.
所以如果你有一个弱点，最终，人们会发现它，
So if you have a vulnerability,
eventually, people will find it and
他们就会利用它
they will exploit it.
>> Jem Young: 而 nmap 不会显示的是它们不会显示所有关闭的端口。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And what nmap won't show
is they won't show all the close ports.
它们只显示打开的端口，但您可以扫描已关闭的端口。
They only gonna show the open ports but
you can scan for closed ports.
这一点也不是什么意义。
It's not really much of a point for
that as well.